[{"answer": "Very emotional for me.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "What was it like to see your son elected president?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I think he felt badly for his son, and -- when his son was criticized.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "You, as his friend, what do you think?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Chaz, how are you?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Well, I was just trying to think back to our last encounter, and what an extraordinary twist to your life that's gone on ever since.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "How are you doing?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I mean, I think it put some pressure on the relationship.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "How much pressure did the fact that you had decided to become a man -- how much pressure did that put on the relationship, do you think, looking back?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "You know, I think that she did.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Did you feel that she ever fully embraced what you were doing?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I mean, it wasn't a pleasant thing to do, you know, honestly.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Do you regret doing that, with hindsight?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Yeah I mean, I think we both cared very deeply for each other.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Have you managed to stay friends?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm not the most outgoing fellow.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "How are you finding that?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "You know, I think that it just -- when that first started with those type of people, I just kind of let it roll off my back.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "What did you feel when all that bile was being spilled in your direction?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "You know, as a Democrat I'm always -- and especially after our last Republican president -- I'm concerned to have a Republican in the White House for any number of reason.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "If he becomes president, would that concern you to his position on, as you said, a new civil rights issue in many ways would be pretty intransigent?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I get -- any number of reasons.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "But particularly that one?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "You know, we really -- we really don't.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Do you and your stepmother have lively debates about this, Chaz?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "You know, I'm very excited.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "How excited are you about London?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "That's the picture there.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Like what the heck?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "No, I didn't give up.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "In the last hundredth of a second did you just give up?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "I broke my thumb in the next race.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "You went and broke your thumb?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "I was just -- I couldn't believe I lost by a touch.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Because you were so full of rage?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I didn't know I did it.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "How hard are you hitting that wall to break your thumb?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "That's a good question.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "No man?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Which one are you going to take?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I think I have to shut my mouth more.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I always quaintly assumed that when you get to that stage of the preparation it's like boxers, there's no hanky-panky.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Next?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Of course, I never did anything like that.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "So why not, right?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I'm as old as their mothers.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Did you have your eyes on anybody special this year after -- say you win gold, anyone on the American Olympic squad that you might be the lucky recipient of my joy?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "No, we're not.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Are we going to stand side by side and do it together?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Well, people have to remember I do this for a living.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "OK, let's get to -- women watch this, falling over saying how, how do you keep that six pack looking like that?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Probably between four and six hours.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "For how long?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "I've just done a very thorough research job on you.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Where do you get your information from?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "So did you fire him?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "I don't like to share that, because I don't want to jinx anything.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "What has he said about London?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "And hundreds of millions of people around the world.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "It'll stay between us?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "He's gotten a lot right about my personal life.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "What has he got right?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Well, okay.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "You were having trouble conceiving and he predicted you would have a daughter?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Well, what you do is you go in there and he leaves the room and you take a card and you write down three questions that you want answered and your write down three people who have passed away and you sign and print your name.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Who does he talk to?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "ORRES: I don't have a conversation -- yeah, he's an example, I asked something and my dad came in and he started talking about how my dad only wants me to finish this last one because he wants to see me have a family and you know have that come first.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "And you have a conversation through this man?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Well, I guess I'll find out in a few months.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "Until that's done in your life, do you think you've got a chance?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "I actually would just like to make the Olympic team.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "So one last gold in London?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "120609pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "They will won't you?", "qSentId": 641}]